Guide to the Ohio State University, Office of the President (Harold Leroy Enarson) Records, 1940s-2002 RG.3.J
Ohio State University Libraries Special Collections
Ohio State University, Office of the President (Harold Leroy Enarson) Records
1940s-2002
RG.3.J
Ohio State University Libraries Special Collections
67.14 Cubic feet
The Ohio State University, Office of the President (Harold Leroy Enarson) Records contain correspondence, publications, reports, awards, speeches and other materials related to University business during the Enarson presidency from 1972 to 1981. The collection also contains materials from before and after Enarson's presidency, including chronology and letters concerning the retirement of President Fawcett and the search for his successor and an oral history interview of audio recordings. Harold Enarson was the ninth president of The Ohio State University, serving from 1972 to 1981, establishing the Departments of Black Studies and Women Studies and the Office of Minority Affairs during his term.
(45) cartons, (11) letter file folders, (1) legal file folder, (12) audiocassette tapes, (1) oversize folder, (2) artifacts, (1) 2.5" document box, (3) 5" document boxes
Enarson, Harold L., 1919-2006
Arrangement of Materials
The Processed series is arranged strictly alphabetically, broken down not by series but by box. All other series are arranged in the order received.
Acquisitions Information
Accession Number UA.1977.0122: Office of the President; Accession Number UA.1980.0015: University Publications; Accession Number UA.1981.0041: Office of the President; Accession Number UA.1981.0043: Office of the President; Accession Number UA.1981.0054: Ruth Jones; Accession Number UA.1981.0057: Office of the President; Accession Number UA.1981.0072: News and Information Services; Accession Number UA.1981.0086: Harold Enarson; Accession Number UA.1982.0070: Office of the President; Accession Number UA.1983.0021; Accession Number UA.1983.0074; Accession Number UA.1983.0169; Accession Number UA.1984.0007; Accession Number UA.1985.0053; Accession Number UA.1985.0081; Accession Number UA.1985.0134: Paul Underwood; Accession Number UA.1986.0068; Accession Number UA.1987.0202; Accession Number UA.1991.0034; Accession Number UA.1993.0184; Accession Number UA.1994.0048; Accession Number UA.1996.0086; Accession Number UA.1998.0142: David Scott; Accession Number UA.2000.0038: Darrin Smella, David Bhaerman; Accession Number UA.2000.0113; Accession Number UA.2002.0052: Harold Enarson; Accession Number UA.2003.0123: Harold Enarson; Accession Number UA.2003.0132; Accession Number UA.2008.0093; Accession Number UA.2010.0014: Merlyn Prentice; Accession Number UA.2013.0036: Heather Staley McNamara, 2013; Accession Number UA.2016.0105
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Contains audiocassettes.
Access to Materials
Materials in this collection are available for patron research, but may be used only in the University Archives Reading Room. Audiovisual materials may need a use copy produced before access is allowed. Some materials in this collection may be stored off-site, and are only available if requested 72 hours in advance of your visit. Some materials in this collection have been marked confidential and may be restricted to the public. Contact the University Archives for more information.
Historical Note
Harold Leroy Enarson (1919-2006) was the ninth president of The Ohio State University, serving from 1972 to 1981.
Born in Villisca, Iowa in 1919, Harold Leroy Enarson grew up in New Mexico. His brother, sister and father all died of tuberculosis, and Harold worked while attending high school to support his mother. He graduated from Albuquerque High School in 1936 with a scholarship to attend the University of New Mexico, where he graduated with honors in 1940.
After graduation, he worked in the Bureau of the Budget in Washington, D.C., and enlisted in the Army after Pearl Harbor. He served in the Army in WWII, in the Pacific and European theaters, from 1943 to 1946, when he was wounded in Germany. After World War II, he finished his master's degree at Stanford University and resumed his position as a budget examiner for the U.S. Bureau of the Budget.
Enarson taught at Stanford, served as executive secretary to the Steel Industry Board and as a consultant to the National Security Resources Board. He earned his Ph.D. in political science from American University in 1951 before serving two years as labor affairs assistant on the staff of President Harry S. Truman. In 1954, he took up the position of assistant director of commerce for the City of Philadelphia, and served as executive secretary to the mayor of Philadelphia. He also spent six years as executive director of the Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education (WICHE), based in Boulder, Colorado. WICHE was designed to improve cooperation and resource-sharing among higher education administrations in the West.
Enarson's academic career began when he was named Administrative Vice President at the University of New Mexico in 1960, becoming the Academic Vice President a year later. There he created a four-year medical school, and he developed one of the nation's largest Peace Corps training programs for Latin America. He was later awarded the James F. Zimmerman Award for his contributions. In 1965, Enarson accepted the presidency of the newly established Cleveland State University, a position he would hold until 1972.
During the tumult of the Vietnam years, Enarson worked to encourage student participation and ensure that student's voices were heard and to increase enrollment of women and minorities. His presidency of Ohio State University began in 1972, and he immediately went to work to protect the University's funding during a time of state budget cuts. He was also a Professor of Public Policy and Management. He oversaw great changes on campus, including the establishment of the Departments of Black Studies and Women Studies, the Office of Minority Affairs and the OSU Child Care Center.
After retiring in 1981 as President Emeritus, Enarson was a senior advisor to WICHE and a commissioner on the Colorado Commission on Higher Education for 15 years, and served on a special oversight committee established by the Northern District Court of Alabama to respond to Title VI remedy actions on racial discrimination in universities. In 1992, he received the "Distinguished Service Award" as Public Higher Education Board Member of the Year from the Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges. Harold Enarson died on July 28, 2006, in Port Townsend, Washington.
Scope and Contents
The Ohio State University, Office of the President (Harold Leroy Enarson) Records contain correspondence, publications, reports, committee reports, appointment schedules, awards, speeches and other materials related to University business during the Enarson presidency from 1972 to 1981. The collection also contains materials from before and after Enarson's presidency, including a framed portrait and bronze plaque, biographical notes, chronology and letters concerning the retirement of President Fawcett and the search for his successor, correspondence between Enarson and his mother while he was working in Washington, D.C., and an oral history interview transcript and audiocassette recordings.
Related Materials
RG 3.J.5
Audrey Enarson Papers
RG 40.191
Harold L. Enarson Papers
Ohio State University Archives Biographical File
Harold L. Enarson
Enarson, Harold L., 1919-2006; Fawcett, Novice G. (Novice Gail), 1909-; Ohio State University--Administration.; Ohio State University--History.; Ohio State University--Presidents.; Affirmative action programs in education--Ohio--Columbus--20th century; College administrators--Ohio--Columbus--20th century; College administrators--Selection and appointment--Ohio--Columbus--20th century; College presidents--Ohio--Columbus--20th century; Cultural artifacts; Disabilities--United States--History; Minorities--Education (Higher)--Ohio--Columbus--20th century; State universities and colleges--Ohio--Columbus--Administration--20th century; United States--Social conditions--1960-1980; Women--Education (Higher)--Ohio--Columbus--20th century
- Processed, 1971-1981; 54.0 Cubic feet; (45) cartons
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains correspondence, publications, reports, speeches and other materials related to University business during the Enarson presidency from 1972 through 1981. The date range for collection materials is 1971 to 1981.
  - Academic Affairs: Council on, 1973-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0001, Folder 1)
  - Academic Affairs: Office of the Provost: Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0001, Folder 2)
  - Academic Affairs: Office of the Provost: Corresopndence, 1975-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0001, Folder 3)
  - Academic Affairs: Office of the Provost: Correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0001, Folder 4)
  - Academic Affairs: Office of the Provost: Search Correspondence, 1979 January-March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0001, Folder 5)
    Conditions Governing Access note
    CONFIDENTIAL
  - Academic Affairs: Office of the Provost: Search Correspondence, 1979 April-June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0001, Folder 6)
    Confidential.
  - Academic Affairs: Office of the Provost: A.P. Sloan Foundation Self-Study: 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0001, Folder 7)
  - Academic Misconduct: Committee On:, 1973-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0001, Folder 8)
  - Academy for Academic Problems:, 1974-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0001, Folder 9)
  - Academy for Contemporary Problems: Correspondence:, 1972-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0001, Folder 10)
  - Activities Center: University:, 1972 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0001, Folder 11)
  - Administration And Faculty:, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0001, Folder 12)
  - Administrative Council:, 1973-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0001, Folder 13)
  - Administrative Operations: Vice-President for:, 1972 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0001, Folder 14)
  - Administrative Operations: Vice-President for:, 1973 January-June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0001, Folder 15)
  - Administrative Operations: Vice-President for:, 1973 July-December (Box UA.RG.3.J.0001, Folder 16)
  - Administrative Operations: Vice-President for:, 1976 March-August (Box UA.RG.3.J.0001, Folder 17)
  - Administrative Operations: Vice-President for:, 1976 July-September (Box UA.RG.3.J.0001, Folder 18)
  - Administrative Operations: Vice-President for: Annual Reports:, 1976 April-December (Box UA.RG.3.J.0001, Folder 19)
  - Administrative Operations: Vice-President for: Energy Conservation Program:, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0001, Folder 20)
  - Administrative Operations: Vice-President for: Occupational Safety and Health Program Committee:, 1975 December-1976 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0001, Folder 21)
  - Administrative Operations: Vice-President for: Program Committees:, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0001, Folder 22)
  - Administrative Science: College of: Accreditation of Public Administration, 1976-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 1)
  - Administrative Science: American Assembly of Collegiate Schools of Business, 1976-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Sciences: American Council on Education, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 3)
  - Administrative Science: Bulletin of Business Research, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 4)
  - Administrative Science: Continuing Education, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 5)
  - Administrative Science: College of: Correspondence, 1972-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 6)
  - Administrative Science: Faculty, 1972-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 7)
  - Administrative Science: Grants, 1977-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 8)
  - Administrative Science: "Measurement of Outcomes of Management Education-A Feasibility Study", 1980 April 6 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 9)
  - Administrative Science: Minority Assistance Program, 1976-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 10)
  - Administrative Science: Ohio Council of Economic Education: Annual Report, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 11)
  - Administrative Science: Peer Review, 1977-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 12)
  - Administrative Science: Promotion and Tenure, 1972-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 13)
  - Administrative Science: Scholarship Committee, 1974-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 14)
  - Administrative Science: Search Committee, 1973-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 15)
  - Administrative Systems: Executive Director, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 16)
  - Administrators and Academic Officials: Review, 1978-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 17)
  - Admission Policies for Graduate Professional Programs: Task Force Report, 1975 July (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 18)
  - Admissions: Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act Guidelines, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 19)
  - Admissions: Office of: Graduate and Professional: Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 20)
  - Admissions: Office of: Graduate and Professional: Correspondence, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 21)
  - Admissions: Office of: Graduate and Professional: Correspondence, 1976-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 22)
  - Admissions: Graduate and Professional: Requirements and Procedures, 1974-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 23)
  - Admissions: Orin Slagle Committee, 1976-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 24)
  - Admissions: Summary of Admission Policies and Procedures, 1972 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 25)
  - Admissions: Task Force on Admission Policies for Graduate Professional Programs: Observations, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 26)
  - Admissions: Undergraduate: Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 27)
  - Admissions: Undergraduate: Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 28)
  - Admissions: Undergraduate: Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 29)
  - Admissions: Undergraduate: Freshman Scholar Packet, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 30)
  - Admissions: Undergraduate: Proposed Task Force for Recruitment, 1972 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 31)
  - Admissions: Undergraduate: Report: Overview of ACT Test Score Decline, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 32)
  - Admissions and Allocations Committee: Minutes, 1973-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 33)
  - Admissions and Registration: Council on: Minutes (incl. Final Report), 1973-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 34)
  - Advertising: Correspondence, 1973-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 35)
  - Affirmative Action: Annual Report, 1971-1972 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 36)
  - Affirmative Action: Annual Report, 1972-1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 37)
  - Affirmative Action: Annual Report, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0002, Folder 38)
  - Affirmative Action: Annual Report, 1975-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0003, Folder 1)
  - Affirmative Action: Center for Vocational Education, 1976-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0003, Folder 2)
  - Affirmative Action: College of Administrative Science, 1976 February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0003, Folder 3)
  - Affirmative Action: College of Dentistry, 1975 July (Box UA.RG.3.J.0003, Folder 4)
  - Affirmative Action: College of Humanities, 1976 February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0003, Folder 5)
  - Affirmative Action: College of Medicine, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0003, Folder 6)
  - Affirmative Action: Commission on Women and Minorities, 1975-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0003, Folder 7)
  - Affirmative Action: Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0003, Folder 8)
  - Affirmative Action: Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0003, Folder 9)
  - Affirmative Action: Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0003, Folder 10)
  - Affirmative Action: OSU Hospitals, 1974-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0003, Folder 11)
  - Affirmative Action: Search for Assistant Director, 1974-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0003, Folder 12)
  - Affirmative Action: Search for Director, 1975-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0003, Folder 13)
  - Affirmative Action: Sloan, Rose, 1972-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0003, Folder 14)
  - Affirmative Action Materials: Batey, Charles, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0003, Folder 15)
  - Affirmative Action Plan (Revised), 1978 January (Box UA.RG.3.J.0003, Folder 16)
  - Affirmative Action Plan (Revised), 1978 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0003, Folder 17)
  - Affirmative Action Plan (Revised), 1979 September (Box UA.RG.3.J.0003, Folder 18)
  - Affirmative Action Report, 1976-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0003, Folder 19)
  - Affirmative Action Report, 1978-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0003, Folder 20)
  - Affirmative Action Statement, 1977-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0003, Folder 21)
  - Africa Trip, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0003, Folder 22)
  - Agency on International Development: Reports, 1972-1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0003, Folder 23)
  - Agriculture and Home Economics: College of: Agricultural Engineering Research Report, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0003, Folder 24)
  - Agriculture and Home Economics: Barneby Center: Letters Regarding, 1977-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0003, Folder 25)
  - Agriculture and Home Economics: Brazil Relations, 1974-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0003, Folder 26)
  - Agriculture and Home Economics: Byg, Professor Delbert, case, 1978-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0003, Folder 27)
  - Agriculture and Home Economics: CARE Report, 1979-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0003, Folder 28)
  - Agriculture and Home Economics:Chadwick Aboretum, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0003, Folder 29)
  - Agriculture and Home Economics: China Agreements, 1979-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0003, Folder 30)
  - Agriculture and Home Economics: Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0003, Folder 31)
  - Agriculture and Home Economics: Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0003, Folder 32)
  - Agriculture and Home Economics: Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0003, Folder 33)
  - Agriculture and Home Economics: Hone, Cathy: Situation, 1978-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0003, Folder 34)
  - Agriculture and Home Economics: Manpower Study, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0003, Folder 35)
  - Agriculture and Home Economics: Moores Demonstration: Farm, 1979-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0003, Folder 36)
  - Agriculture and Home Economics: Project Outline for OARDC and Cooperative Extension: Communication System, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0003, Folder 37)
  - Alcoholic Beverages: Correspondence, 1972 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0004, Folder 1)
  - Alcoholic Beverages: Correspondence, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0004, Folder 2)
  - Alcoholic Beverages: Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0004, Folder 3)
  - Alcoholic Beverages: Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0004, Folder 4)
  - Alcoholic Beverages: Evaluation and Recommendations, 1972 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0004, Folder 5)
  - Alcoholic Beverages: Proposed Revision of University Regulations Concerning Alcohol, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0004, Folder 6)
  - Alcoholic Beverages: Statement by Harold Enarson; Alcoholic Beverages on Campus, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0004, Folder 7)
  - Allied Health Education: Accreditation: Current Issues and Concerns, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0004, Folder 8)
  - Allied Medical Services: School of: Correspondence:, 1973-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0004, Folder 9)
  - Alumni Advisory Board: Correspondence, 1972-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0004, Folder 10)
  - Alumni Advisory Board: Scholarships, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0004, Folder 11)
  - Alumni Association: Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0004, Folder 12)
  - Alumni Association: Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0004, Folder 13)
  - Alumni Association: Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0004, Folder 14)
  - Alumni Association: Report: Attracting the Non-Traditional Student, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0004, Folder 15)
  - Alumni Association: Sphinx 75th Anniversary Gift Committee, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0004, Folder 16)
  - Alumni Association: Survey of Foreign Alumni, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0004, Folder 17)
  - Alumni Distinguished Teaching Awards: Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0004, Folder 18)
  - Alumni Distinguished Teaching Awards: Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0004, Folder 19)
  - Alumni Monthly: Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0004, Folder 20)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Slavic Studies, 1973-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0004, Folder 21)
  - American Association for Higher Education: Chicago Conference: Papers, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0004, Folder 22)
  - American Association for Higher Education: Chicago Conference: Correspondence and Minutes, 1974-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0004, Folder 23)
  - American Association of Universities (AAU): Correspondence, Memoranda, and Minutes, 1972-1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0004, Folder 24)
  - American Association of Universities (AAU): Correspondence, Memoranda, and Minutes, 1974-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0004, Folder 25)
  - American Association of Universities (AAU): Correspondence, Memoranda, and Minutes, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0004, Folder 26)
  - American Association of Universities (AAU): Council on Federal Relations, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0004, Folder 27)
  - American Association of Universities (AAU): Council on Postsecondary Accreditation (COPA): Committee on Recognition, 1979-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0004, Folder 28)
  - American Association of Universities (AAU): Correspondence, Memoranda, Minutes and Reports, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0004, Folder 29)
  - American Association of Universities (AAU): Correspondence, Memoranda, Minutes and Reports, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0004, Folder 30)
  - American Association of Universities (AAU): Council on Postsecondary Accrediation (COPA): Correspondence, Memoranda, Minutes, and Reports, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0005, Folder 1)
  - American Association of University Professors: AAUP Statement to OSU Board of Trustees, 1977 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0005, Folder 2)
  - American Association of University Professors: AAUP Surveys, 1977-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0005, Folder 3)
  - American Association of University Professors: Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0005, Folder 4)
  - American Association of University Professors: Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0005, Folder 5)
  - American Association of University Professors: Correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0005, Folder 6)
  - American Association of University Professors: Faculty Salary Difference by Sex, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0005, Folder 7)
  - American Association of University Professors: Report: Academic Freedom and Tenure, 1972 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0005, Folder 8)
  - American Association of University Professors: Tenure and Promotion: Remarks, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0005, Folder 9)
  - American Association of University Women, 1973-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0005, Folder 10)
  - American Council on Education (ACE): Academic Intern Program: Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0005, Folder 11)
  - American Council on Education (ACE): Committee on International Athletics, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0005, Folder 12)
  - American Council on Education (ACE): Correspondence, 1972-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0005, Folder 13)
  - American Council on Learned Societies: Correspondence, 1973-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0005, Folder 14)
  - American Society for Public Administration, 1975 January-March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0005, Folder 15)
  - Anesthesiology: Dept. of: Allegations, 1978-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0005, Folder 16)
  - Archivist: University, 1973-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0005, Folder 17)
  - Argonne Universities Association: Correspondence, 1973-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0005, Folder 18)
  - Arts: College of: Correspondence, 1972-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0005, Folder 19)
  - Arts and Sciences: College of: Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0005, Folder 20)
  - Arts and Sciences: College of: Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0005, Folder 21)
  - Arts and Sciences: College of: Report: Trends in Undergraduate Education, 1972 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0005, Folder 22)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1976-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0005, Folder 23)
  - Association of Governing Boards of State Universities: Correspondence, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0005, Folder 24)
  - Association of Universities for Research in Astronomy, 1971-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0005, Folder 25)
  - Association of Urban Universities, 1970-1972 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0005, Folder 26)
  - Athletic Council: Correspondence, 1972-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0005, Folder 27)